Do you have any shoes like these?
像这样的鞋子你们有吗?
What size?
什么尺码的?
Size five.
5号的.
what color?
什么颜色?
Black.
黑的
I'm sorry.
对不起,
We don't have any.
我们没有.
But my sister bought this pair last month.
但是,我姐姐上个月买了这双.
Did she buy them here?
她是在这儿买的吗?
No, she bought them in the U. S.
不.她是在美国买的.
We had some shoes like those a month ago,
一个月前我们有这样的鞋,
but we don't have any now.
但是现在没有了.
Can you get a pair for me, please?
您能为我弄一双吗?
I'm afraid that I can't.
恐怕不行.
They were in fashion last year and the year before last.
这鞋在去年和前年流行,
But they're not in fashion this year.
而今年已不流行了.
These shoes are in fashion now.
现在流行的是这种鞋子.
They look very uncomfortable.
这种鞋子看上去很不舒适.
They are very uncomfortable.
的确很不舒适.
But women always wear uncomfortable shoes!
可是女人们总是穿不舒适的鞋子!